bannedinhollywood.com 2018-03-16

# Privacy Policy – BANNED IN HOLLYWOOD

**Privacy Policy**

**Effective Date:**  February 7, 2016

This Privacy Policy explains how Bannedinhollywood and its subsidiaries ( **“Bannedinhollywood”** ) collect, use, and disclose information, and your choices for managing your information preferences.

**What This Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy describes Bannedinhollywood’s data practices associated with our corporate website (www.Bannedinhollywood.com) and Bannedinhollywood services ( **“Services”** ), and the choices that Bannedinhollywood provides in connection with our collection and use of your information. This Privacy Policy is intended for both website publisher customers ( **“Publishers”** ) and individual users of websites and apps. For Publishers, this Policy explains how Bannedinhollywood may collect, use and disclose information associated with your company and with your company’s websites and apps that use Bannedinhollywood Services. For individual website and app users, this Privacy Policy explains how Bannedinhollywood may collect, use, and disclose information when you visit our website or when you use any website or app that uses Bannedinhollywood Services.

Bannedinhollywood Services include our Ad Exchange, a Web-based marketplace that enables publishers, advertisers, and ad networks to efficiently market, buy and sell digital and mobile advertising and ad inventory. Bannedinhollywood also offers services, such as our Ad Server, through which we act as a service provider to enable our Publishers, advertisers, ad networks, and other clients to manage their advertising inventory and to collect and use data to provide advertising on their digital and mobile properties and across the Internet. In this case, Publishers may use our services to process data, which they collect or source. Publishers and other clients may also have their own policies that govern how they collect, use, and share data. These policies may differ from Bannedinhollywood’s policies described in this Privacy Policy. Please consult the privacy policies of the websites you visit and apps you use to become familiar with their privacy practices and to learn about any choices that these companies may offer with respect to their information practices.

Finally, the Bannedinhollywood website may contain links to websites or content operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of a third-party website before disclosing any information to the website.

**Information Collection and Use**

Bannedinhollywood collects contact information through our website when you choose to provide it, such as your name, username, or email address. For example, you may be asked to provide us with contact information when you register with the Bannedinhollywood website and when you purchase the Services. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you elect not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to access certain content, features, or services available on or through the Bannedinhollywood website. In order to make payments owed to Publishers, Bannedinhollywood may also request additional information from Publishers such as other contact information and billing account information.

Bannedinhollywood uses this contact and billing information to operate and improve our website and Services, such as to provide notices about your Service, to fulfill your service requests, or to request your feedback or conduct research. Bannedinhollywood also uses contact information to send you information about new products or Services; where Bannedinhollywood needs your permission to do this, we only send such information in accordance with any permissions granted.

We may also collect additional information through our website and Services, such as the following:

  * ‘Free form’ demographic information (e.g. age, gender, marital status)
  * Browser information (e.g. URL, browser type, ‘click through’ data)
  * Ad reporting or delivery data (e.g. size/type of ad, ad impressions, location/format of ad, data about interactions with the ad)
  * Device-type information (e.g. screen dimensions, device brand and model)
  * Unique identification numbers (e.g. IP address and mobile/cell phone device ID)
  * Location data (as derived from IP address or GPS (for mobile))
  * Interest segments (i.e. inferred information on the behavior or likely interests associated with a device)
  * Retargeting data (i.e. data revealing previous interest in a product or website)
  * Information about the possible relationships among different browsers and devices

With respect to data collected via the Bannedinhollywood Ad Exchange, we may combine information that does not directly identify an individual with data collected from other sources and disclose the combined information to participating publishers, advertisers and ad networks so that they can determine whether to bid on ad inventory and in order to improve the relevance of the advertising presented to users. We also use the information we collect to host, operate, maintain, secure, and further develop and improve our Services, such as to keep track of advertising delivery and to measure the effectiveness of advertising delivered through our Services, and investigate compliance with Bannedinhollywood’s policies and terms and conditions.

Bannedinhollywood does not engage in activities that require parental notice or consent under the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). If you believe that Bannedinhollywood has inadvertently collected information from a child under 13 that is subject to parental notice and consent under COPPA, please contact Bannedinhollywood using the contact information below to request deletion of the information.

**_Cookies and Web Beacons._**  We use cookies (a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your Web browser), Web beacons (an electronic file placed within a Web site that monitors usage), pixels, etags, and similar technologies to operate and improve our website and Services, including for interest-based advertising as described below. Some of our Service Providers (defined below) may also use such technologies in connection with the services they perform on our behalf.

We use the following categories of cookies for our website and Services:

  * **Strictly Necessary Cookies**

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to navigate our website and use its features. Without these cookies, Services you have asked for such as remembering your login details cannot be provided.

  * **Performance Cookies**

These cookies collect anonymous information on how people use our website. For example, we use these cookies to help us understand how customers arrive at our site, browse or use our site and highlight areas where we can improve, such as navigation and marketing campaigns. The data stored by these cookies never shows personal details from which your individual identity can be established.

  * **Functionality Cookies**

These cookies remember choices you make such as the country from which you visit our website, language and search parameters such as size, color or product line. These cookies can then be used to provide you with an experience more appropriate to your selections and to make the visits more tailored and relevant. The information these cookies collect may be anonymized and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites. ** **

  * **Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies**

These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. The cookies remember the websites you visit and that information is shared with other parties such as advertisers. Please see our Interest-Based Advertising section below for information about your choices regarding our use of these technologies for interest-based advertising.

Publishers, advertisers and third-party ad networks that participate in the Bannedinhollywood Ad Exchange may also utilize cookies or similar technologies to deliver ads and monitor the performance of such ads. The collection of information through cookies or similar technologies by such third parties will be governed by their own privacy policies and principles, which Bannedinhollywood does not control.

Your browser may offer tools to enable or disable cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, please note that certain features of the Bannedinhollywood website may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Moreover, if you delete cookies after previously opting out of Bannedinhollywood’s Ad Exchange practices, you may need to renew your opt-out choice. To read about your choices with regard to Bannedinhollywood’s use of cookies in our services, please see below.

**Information Sharing**

We will disclose contact and billing information to third parties only as described in this Privacy Policy:

  * with your express permission;
  * with our affiliates, which include entities controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Bannedinhollywood;
  * where we contract with third parties to provide certain services, such as advertising, analytics, data management services, web hosting, and web development ( **“Service Providers”** ). We ask Service Providers to confirm that their privacy and security practices are consistent with ours, we provide our Service Providers with only the information necessary for them to perform the services we request, and Service Providers are prohibited from using such information for purposes other than as specified by Bannedinhollywood;
  * in the event that Bannedinhollywood is merged, sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets (including in bankruptcy), or in the event of another corporate change, we may disclose or transfer information in connection with such transaction; and
  * where we believe it is necessary to protect Bannedinhollywood or our users; to enforce our terms or the legal rights of Bannedinhollywood or others; or to comply with a request from governmental authorities, legal process, or other legal obligations.

We may also share and disclose other information that we collect, including aggregate information, as we consider necessary to develop and provide our Services, including in the ways described above. The information that we share in this way would not, in the United States, be considered to personally identify an individual.

**Interest-Based Advertising and Opting Out**

Bannedinhollywood adheres to the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) Self-Regulatory Principles in the US and to the European Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA) Principles in the EU and the IAB Europe OBA Framework.

[As discussed above](http://openx.com/legal/privacypolicy/#information_collection_and_use), the Bannedinhollywood Ad Exchange uses cookies, Web beacons, pixels, etags, and similar technologies to give Publishers the possibility to offer, and Ad Exchange advertisers the ability to show, targeted ads on the device on which you are viewing this policy or a different device. These ads are more likely to be relevant to you because they are based on inferences drawn from location data, web viewing data collected across non-affiliated sites over time, and/or application use data collected across non-affiliated apps over time. This is called “interest-based advertising.” In addition, certain third parties may collect data on the Bannedinhollywood website and combine this data with information collected from other websites over time for purposes that include interest-based advertising.

**_Opting Out from a Browser that Permits Cookies:  _**If you would like to learn more about this type of advertising, or would prefer to opt out of website interest-based advertising enabled by Bannedinhollywood’s Ad Exchange, US residents may visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) to opt out of this form of advertising by companies participating in the DAA self-regulatory program and European Union residents may opt-out of this form of advertising by companies participating in the EDAA at [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). Note that if your browser does not accept third-party cookies, you may not be able make choices via these tools. Refer to the ‘Opting Out from a Browser that Blocks Cookies’ section to learn more.

**_Opting Out for Application Data:  _**To opt out of Bannedinhollywood’s collection and use of data for interest-based advertising on mobile apps, US residents may download the DAA’s AppChoices application from the Android or iOS app store on your mobile device.

**_Opting Out for Location Data:  _**You may opt out of our collection and use of precise location data by using the location services controls in your mobile device’s settings.

**_Opting Out from a Browser that Blocks Cookies:  _**Please note that in order for your opt-out choice to be effective, you must ensure that your browser is set to accept third-party cookies such as the Bannedinhollywood opt-out cookie. Some browsers block third-party cookies by default, and you may need to change your browser settings to accept third-party cookies before opting out.

**_Effect of Opting Out:  _**If you use a different device or browser, or erase cookies from your browser, you will need to renew your opt-out choice.

If you opt out of Bannedinhollywood’s practices, you may continue to receive interest-based advertising through other companies. Third-party advertisers and ad networks that participate in the Bannedinhollywood Ad Exchange may also use their own cookies and other ad service technologies to display and track their ads. We do not control and are not responsible for such third-party advertisers’ and ad networks’ information practices or their use of cookies and other ad service technologies. To learn more about the practices of these companies, please read their privacy policies.

Even if you opt-out, Bannedinhollywood may continue to collect data for other purposes and you still will receive advertising from the Bannedinhollywood Ad Exchange when you visit websites of a Publisher who uses our Services – but such advertising will not be targeted to you.

**Reviewing and Updating Information**

Bannedinhollywood takes reasonable steps to ensure that information is accurate, complete, current, and reliable for its intended use. For contact or billing information submitted through our website, you may review, correct, update, or change your information, request that we delete your information, or remove your information from our direct marketing efforts, at any time by e-mailing us at  _[darren@bannedinhollywood.com](mailto:darren@Bannedinhollywood.com)_.

**International Information Transfers**

Please be aware that the information we collect, including contact and billing information, may be transferred to and maintained on servers or databases located outside your state, province, country, or other jurisdiction, where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your location. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that we process and store information in the United States and your consent to this Privacy Policy represents your agreement and understanding to this processing.

**Security**

Information that we collect is stored using procedures and practices reasonably designed to help protect information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.

**Policy Updates**

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Bannedinhollywood website. Those changes will go into effect on the effective date disclosed in the revised Privacy Policy.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Bannedinhollywood Privacy Policy, please contact us by e-mailing us at [darren@bannedinhollywood.com](mailto:mirza@bluTonic.com).
